export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Who is the only team to defeat the Celtics at Boston (Madison Square) Garden during the 1985-1986 season?",
    answers: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Dallas Maverics",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "George Gervin’s 'most points scored in a quarter’ record was broken in 2015, by this player—who still holds the record today.",
    answers: ["Kevin Durant", "LeBron James", "Stephen Curry", "Klay Thompson"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "The National Basketball Association was originally called what?",
    answers: [
      "The Basketball Association of America",
      "The America baseball association",
      "Nation Basketball League",
      "National basketball games",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which player has the most career blocks in the Finals?",
    answers: [
      "Dwight Howard",
      "Boban Marjanovic",
      "Hassan Whiteside",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "This player had the most 3-point field goals, during one series of the Finals.",
    answers: ["Ray Allen", "Steph Curry", "Peja Stajakovic", "Kevin Durant"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What NBA team was the first to win 70 games in one season?",
    answers: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "This famous rapper is often seen courtside at NBA team’s games?",
    answers: ["Drake", "Baggy B", "Lil Wayne", "Kendrick Lamar"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team beat the 1996 Chicago Bulls record 72 wins in a season?",
    answers: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the team famously named, that America sent to the 1992 Olympics, when professionals were allowed to play?",
    answers: [
      "The Super Team",
      "The Famous Team",
      "The Dream Team",
      "The Superstars Team",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the legendary player known as 'Half man half amazing'?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Tracy McGrady",
      "Vince Carter",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
];
